- Check out the cool, older kids over there.
- 看看那边那些酷酷的大孩子。
- Looks like they've got a Ricky in their group, too.
- 看起来他们那组也有个叫Ricky的。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- That is Ricky.
- 那就是Ricky。
- Our Ricky?
- 我们的Ricky？
Are you sure it's not me?
你确定不是我吗？
Because I'd make more sense.
因为那样更合理。
- How could it be you?
- 怎么可能是你？
You're sitting right here.
你明明就坐在这里。
Ricky's over there.
Ricky在那边。
- That's what makes no sense.
- 这才是说不通的。
- Miles, I'm telling you,
- 迈尔斯，我告诉你，
they're not gonna want to play laser tag.
他们不会想玩激光标签的。
They said they're over it.
他们说他们已经玩腻了。
- Let me handle it.
- 让我来处理。
I've got a way to make it sound
我有办法让它听起来
cool and exciting.
既酷又刺激。
Hey, guys,
嘿，伙计们，
want to play some "laze-tag?"
想玩点“laze-tag”吗？
- Ooh, laze-tag.
- 哦，laze-tag。
That sounds cool and exciting.
听起来很酷很刺激。
- He means laser tag.
- 他是说激光枪战。
- Ooh, laser tag...
- 哦，激光枪战...
then no.
那就不去了。
- Come on, man. - Come on.
- 拜托，伙计。 - 拜托。
- Oh, no, it looks like they're shaking Ricky down.
- 哦，不，看起来他们在找Ricky的麻烦。
He needs backup.
他需要支援。
Aren't you guys coming?
你们不来吗？
- Our fries just got here.
- 我们的薯条刚送来。
- Are you serious?
- 你是认真的吗？
Our brother needs us.
我们的兄弟需要我们。
- Okay, fine.
好吧，好吧。
Can we get a to-go box?
我们可以拿个外卖盒吗？
- No, come on.
不行，快点。
- Don't eat our fries.
别吃我们的薯条。
Our brother needs us.
我们的兄弟需要我们。
- Uh...
呃...
Excuse me, older kids. Is our brother in there?
打扰一下，大孩子们。我们的兄弟在里面吗？
- Not now. He's busy.
现在不行。他正忙着。
He's up to nine quarters on each elbow.
他每个手肘上都叠了九个硬币。
- If I catch these, I'll break my record.
如果我能抓住这些，我就能打破我的记录。
It's show time.
表演时间到了。
- Wait, so you guys are actually hanging out with him?
等等，你们真的在和他一起玩？
- I said, "It's show time."
我说了，‘表演时间到了。’
- So hanging out is some kind of school project?
所以一起玩是某种学校项目吗？
- Arms cramping.
手臂抽筋了。
Show time!
表演时间！
- Wait! - What?
等等！
- Sorry.
什么？
I thought I saw Miles eating our fries.
抱歉。我以为我看到迈尔斯在吃我们的薯条。
Go ahead. Show time.
开始吧。表演时间。
[quarters bouncing]
[硬币弹跳声]
Not much of a show.
没什么好看的。
- See what I have to live with?
- 看看我得忍受什么？
[laughing]
[笑声]
- You did not lie.
- 你没说谎。
- They're sharing a laugh.
- 他们在笑。
What's going on?
怎么回事？
- I'm Zeus.
- 我是宙斯。
This is Jade and Elijah.
这是Jade和Elijah。
- Uh, yeah, we know who you are.
嗯，是的，我们知道你是谁。
I mean, we've seen you guys around school.
我的意思是，我们在学校里见过你们。
- We've seen you guys around school, too.
我们在学校里也见过你们。
- Okay, now I'm going to say it out loud,
好吧，我现在要大声说出来，
"What is going on?"
“到底发生了什么？”
- I'll tell you what's going on.
我会告诉你发生了什么。
We're gonna go play some laze tag.
我们要去玩一些激光标签。
- You guys in?
你们一起来吗？
- We love laze tag!
我们喜欢激光标签！
- It's cool! - And exciting.
太酷了！而且很刺激。
[laughter]
- Did they just blow you off to go play laser tag
- 他们是不是为了去和那些大孩子玩激光枪战而拒绝了你？
with those older kids?
- 和那些大孩子一起？
- Yup.
- 是的。
- Want to eat their fries?
- 想吃他们的薯条吗？
- Yup. Can we eat their fries?
- 是的。我们可以吃他们的薯条吗？
- Yup.
- 是的。
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[cheerful music]
[欢快的音乐]
[together] Whoa.
[一起] 哇。
- No way. Is that really your car?
- 不可能吧。那真的是你的车吗？
- Yep. Bought it with the money I made at my job.
- 是的。用我工作赚的钱买的。
[together] Whoa.
[一起] 哇。
- No way.
- 不可能吧。
Is that really your job?
那真的是你的工作吗？
- No, that's a picture of LeBron James.
- 不，那是勒布朗·詹姆斯的照片。
I work at a movie theater.
我在电影院工作。
- With LeBron James?
- 和勒布朗·詹姆斯一起？
- No. No LeBron James.
- 不，没有勒布朗·詹姆斯。
- He does get free movie passes though.
- 不过他的确能拿到免费电影票。
- Man.
- 天哪。
LeBron James gets everything.
勒布朗·詹姆斯什么都有。
- Anyway, I can hook you guys up with movie passes any time.
- 总之，我随时可以帮你们弄到电影票。
[together] Whoa.
[一起] 哇哦。
- Hey kids, let's wrap it up. It's getting late.
嘿，孩子们，我们收拾一下吧。天色已晚。
- Ooh, I call first bath.
哦，我要先洗澡。
It was cool hanging out with you guys.
和你们一起玩得很开心。
- First bath?
先洗澡？
- Did he say bath?
他说洗澡了吗？
He means shave.
他是说刮胡子。
- Yeah, we all shave.
是啊，我们都刮胡子。
- Big shavers. Yeah.
大刮胡刀。对。
- So, I guess we should bolt then.
那么，我想我们该走了。
- Aw, wow, it's a bummer this fun night is over.
哇，真遗憾，这个愉快的夜晚结束了。
- I mean, it doesn't have to be.
我是说，没必要这样。
You could sneak out and meet us for a late night hang.
你可以偷偷溜出来，和我们一起深夜聚会。
- Sneak out? - Meet up?
偷偷溜出来？
- Will LeBron be there?
聚会？
- Hey, you know what I just thought of?
勒布朗会在那里吗？
Get Sporty would be the perfect place to meet up.
嘿，你知道我刚刚想到什么吗？
- That's a great idea.
Get Sporty会是个完美的聚会地点。
It's got everything: food, foosball,
那是个好主意。
unlimited laze tag.
那里什么都有：食物，桌上足球，
Uh, but I mean, if you guys have baths
还有不限次数的激光标签游戏。
or shaves or whatever, we get it.
或者刮胡子之类的，我们都懂。
We were your age once.
我们也曾经是你们这个年纪。
- No.
- 不。
We may look our age,
我们可能看起来像我们的年纪，
but we're definitely not our age.
但我们绝对不是我们的年纪。
- Yeah, we're big sneaker-outers.
- 是的，我们是超级运动鞋迷。
- The only thing we do more than shave is sneak.
- 我们做的比刮胡子更多的事情就是偷偷摸摸。
- Well, Get Sporty it is then.
- 好吧，那就去Get Sporty吧。
You guys are cooler than we thought.
你们比我们想象的还要酷。
- Has anybody seen my other loofah?
- 有人看到我的另一个丝瓜络了吗？
Ugh, this one's turned.
呃，这个变质了。
Oh, hey, I thought you guys left.
哦，嘿，我以为你们走了。
- We're gonna go now.
我们现在要走了。
See you guys in an hour.
一个小时后见。
- "See you guys in an hour"?
‘一个小时后见’？
- Yeah. I mean,
是啊。我的意思是，
we're sneaking out for a late night hang at Get Sporty.
我们要偷偷出去，在Get Sporty那里深夜聚会。
- Oh. That makes sense.
哦。那说得通。
Are you crazy?
你疯了吗？
We can't sneak out and go for a late night hang at Get Sporty.
我们不能偷偷出去，去Get Sporty那里深夜聚会。
- Well, we have to.
好吧，我们得去。
We promised them, and if we don't show,
我们答应了他们，如果我们不去，
we're gonna look like babies
我们就会看起来像那些不能错过洗澡时间的小宝宝。
who can't miss their bath time.
我们就是那些不能错过洗澡时间的小宝宝！
- We are babies who can't miss their bath time!
好吧，至少对妈妈和爸爸来说，
Okay, at least to Mom and Dad,
但我们不能对他们撒谎。
but we can't lie to them.
我们是他们的宝宝。
We're their babies.
听着，我和其他人一样讨厌对妈妈和爸爸撒谎，
- Look, I hate to lie to Mom and Dad
但我们实际上并没有对他们撒谎。
as much as the next guy,
我们只是没有告诉他们。
but we're not actually lying to them.
但我们并没有对爸妈撒谎。
We're just not telling them.
我们只是没告诉他们而已。
- Oh.
哦。
That makes sense.
这样就合理了。
Are you crazy?
你疯了吗？
- No, I'm rigid and logical, and logic tells me
不，我固执且理性，而理性告诉我这里有酷酷的年长朋友
that there are cool, older friends
和免费的电影票等着我们。
and free movie passes on the line.
所以振作起来，洗澡小子。
So man up, bath boy.
好吧，大家都上床睡觉
- All right, let's all get in bed
这样爸妈才能给我们盖被子，然后我们可以偷偷溜出去。
so Mom and Dad can tuck us in and we can sneak out.
这样爸妈就能给我们盖好被子，然后我们再偷偷溜出去。
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
[music playing in headphones]
[耳机中播放着音乐]
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Hey, hon.
- 嘿，亲爱的。
Hon!
亲爱的！
Hon! - Oh, yeah, yeah.
亲爱的！- 哦，好的，好的。
- Hey, uh, the kids are all tucked in.
- 嘿，呃，孩子们都已经被哄睡了。
I'm gonna go pick up some paper towels
我打算去杂货店买点纸巾。
at the grocery store. - Thanks, okay.
- 谢谢，好的。
[yells] Oh and we're out of loofahs.
哦，我们用完了丝瓜络。
[laughter]
（笑声）
♪ ♪ [door shuts]
♪ ♪ （门关上）
[thud]
（砰的一声）
[inaudible]
（听不清）
- Hi, Squish.
嗨，Squish。
[dog growling]
（狗在低吼）
[phone ringing]
（电话铃响）
Oh.
哦。
Hey, Dawn.
嘿，Dawn。
[inaudible]
Don't blame me.
别怪我。
Maybe if you'd spent more time planning
也许如果你花更多时间计划，
and less time telling me to pay attention,
而不是一直让我注意，
you three wouldn't be out there.
你们三个就不会在外面了。
[inaudible]
Oh.
哦。
Be right there.
马上到。
[rock music]
- I can't believe we actually snuck out
我真不敢相信我们居然偷偷溜出去了，
and now we're sneaking in.
现在我们又偷偷溜回来了。
- Man, I feel so alive.
伙计，我感觉自己充满了活力。
- Yeah, we know.
是啊，我们都知道。
You yelled that the whole way here.
你一路都在大喊大叫。
- All right, our new older friends
好吧，我们新认识的年长朋友们
should be here any minute.
应该随时都会到。
[sniffs]
[嗅]
Oh, what is that smell?
哦，这是什么味道？
- [coughs] Well, normally I'd blame Dicky, but--
嗯，通常我会怪迪基，但是——
- Ugh, it's not even human.
呃，这味道简直不是人能忍受的。
- Is that a challenge?
那是挑战吗？
Because I could work something up.
因为我可以准备点什么。
- Okay, well, if the smell's not coming from one of us,
好吧，如果这味道不是来自我们中的任何一个，
where's it coming from?
那它是从哪儿来的？
[eerie whooshing]
（阴森的呼啸声）
More importantly, where's that coming from?
更重要的是，那声音是从哪儿来的？
- It's probably just the wind.
可能只是风吧。
- [sniffs]
（嗅了嗅）
And a new smell. Jeez.
还有一种新气味。天哪。
- Challenge completed.
挑战完成。
[eerie whooshing]
[阴森的呼啸声]
- Yeah, that is definitely not the wind.
是的，那绝对不是风。
- Then what's with all the mysterious sounds
那么，为什么在一个空无一人的商店里深夜会有这么多神秘的声音和臭味？
and stinks late night at an empty store?
我确信有一个完全合理的解释。
- I'm sure there's a perfectly good explanation.
[阴森的呼啸声]
[eerie whooshing]
是的。比如Get Sporty闹鬼了。
- Yeah. Like Get Sporty's haunted.
Get Sporty没有闹鬼。
- Get Sporty is not haunted.
我们不要再走这条路了。
We are not going down this road again.
记得我们以为爸爸妈妈是僵尸的时候吗？
Remember when we thought Mom and Dad were zombies?
还有Dawn和Dicky是狼人？
- And Dawn and Dicky were werewolves?
- 还有Dawn和Dicky是狼人？
We were wrong both times, just like now.
我们两次都错了，就像现在一样。
[loud eerie whooshing] - Yeah.
[大声的神秘呼啸声] - 是的。
Well, third time's a charm!
好吧，事不过三！
- Fine. Why don't I just ask the ghost
- 好吧。我为什么不直接问鬼魂
if it's really haunted?
这里是不是真的闹鬼？
- Yeah, like he's going to tell you.
- 是啊，好像他会告诉你似的。
- Yo, ghost!
- 喂，鬼魂！
If the store is really haunted,
如果这家店真的闹鬼，
give us a sign.
给我们一个信号。
Thank you, ghost.
谢谢你，鬼魂。
[screaming]
[尖叫声]
- I told you! - I'm out!
- 我告诉过你了！ - 我走了！
- Me first! - No, wait.
- 我先走！ - 不，等等。
What about our older friends?
那我们的老朋友们呢？
They're on their way.
他们已经在路上了。
- What about the ghost?
- 那鬼魂呢？
He's already here.
他已经在这里了。
- I see your point.
- 我明白你的意思。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[rock music]
- See? People are shopping in there.
看？里面有人在购物。
Everything is normal.
一切都很正常。
- That's exactly what the ghost wants you to believe.
那正是鬼魂想让你相信的。
- Nicky, everybody knows hauntings only happen at night.
尼基，大家都知道闹鬼只发生在晚上。
So let's just go in there.
所以我们进去吧。
After you. - After you.
你先请。
- After you. - After you--
[yelling]
你先请。
- Why are you guys so jumpy?
你们为什么这么紧张？
- We're not scared. - Perfectly fine.
- 我们不害怕。 - 完全没问题。
- You're jumpy.
- 你太紧张了。
- So, what happened last night?
- 那么，昨晚发生了什么？
We showed up, but you weren't here.
我们到了，但你不在。
- I told you they chickened out.
- 我告诉过你他们临阵退缩了。
- But it's fine.
- 但没关系。
You guys are bathers, not sneakers.
你们是泡澡的人，不是潜行者。
We understand.
我们理解。
- Thanks for understanding!
- 谢谢你们的理解！
I don't think they understand.
我不认为他们理解。
We totally snuck.
我们完全偷偷进去了。
- But we didn't stay so it voided the snuck.
但我们没有停留，所以不算偷偷进去。
No stay, no snuck.
没有停留，就不算偷偷进去。
- What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办？
- We're gonna say we snuck and why we didn't stay.
我们要说我们偷偷进去了，以及为什么我们没有停留。
That way we'll reinstate the sneak
这样我们就能重新确立偷偷进去的事实，
so they will have to say we snuck.
所以他们将不得不承认我们偷偷进去了。
- You're right...
你说得对...
I think.
我想是的。
Truth always works.
真相总是有效的。
[together] Yeah.
是的。
[laughing]
（笑）
- Haunted?
闹鬼？
- It's true.
这是真的。
There were woo-woos and P.U.'s.
有‘呜呜’声和‘噗’声。
- Were there boo-hoos and wah-wahs, too?
还有‘呜呼’和‘哇哇’声吗？
- A few, but Dawn calmed me down.
有一些，但Dawn让我冷静下来了。
- If you guys are gonna lie,
如果你们要撒谎，
I would at least make it something more believable
我至少会让它听起来更可信
than a ghost baby. [laughing]
而不是一个鬼宝宝。（笑）
- Yeah, let's ghost.
是的，我们走吧。
[imitating a ghost wooing]
[模仿鬼魂的呜咽声]
- I think they just called us liars.
我觉得他们刚刚说我们是骗子。
- You know what?
你知道吗？
I don't care about older friends.
我不在乎年长的朋友。
And I don't care about movie tickets.
我也不在乎电影票。
But I do care about being called "liars."
但我确实在乎被称为“骗子”。
- I think you're lying about the first two things.
我觉得你在前两件事上撒谎了。
- You're darn right I am.
你说得对，我确实撒谎了。
Of course I care about older friends
我当然在乎年长的朋友
and free movie tickets
以及免费电影票
which is why we have
这就是为什么我们必须
to prove this store's haunted
证明这家店闹鬼
and that we're not chickens.
而且我们不是胆小鬼。
- Hey. [startled screaming]
- 嘿。[惊恐尖叫]
- So, now that laze tag is back in,
- 所以，既然激光标签又流行起来了，
you guys want to tag it up?
你们想不想来一场？
- Sorry, guys. We've got stuff to do.
- 抱歉，伙计们。我们有事要做。
- Did I take it too far with the "tag it up"?
- 我是不是说“来一场激光标签”说得太过分了？
- No, it's not you. It's them.
- 不，不是你。是他们。
- I knew I should have gone with "taggy taggy laze laze."
- 我早该用“taggy taggy laze laze”的。
- Then it would've been you.
- 那样的话就是你了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
[music playing in headphones]
[耳机中播放的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Wait, where's Dicky?
- 等等，Dicky去哪儿了？
[thud]
[砰]
[inaudible]
[听不清]
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Okay.
- 好吧。
Ghost hunting equipment.
捉鬼装备。
all: Check.
所有人: 检查完毕。
- Goggles on.
- 戴上护目镜。
all: Check.
所有人: 检查完毕。
- Then let's get to ghost hunting.
- 那我们开始捉鬼吧。
- After you. - After you.
- 您先请。 - 您先请。
- After-- - Okay, enough "after you"-ing.
- 您先—— - 好了，别再‘您先请’了。
Let's just all go together.
我们一起进去吧。
- Right. Back-to-back Quaddle. - Okay.
- 对。背靠背，奎德尔。 - 好的。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- [screams] - What is it?
- [尖叫声] - 那是什么？
- I don't know. It's white.
- 我不知道。它是白色的。
It's spooky, and it's reaching out for me.
它很吓人，而且它正向我伸过来。
Take a look.
看一下。
- [yells]
- [大叫]
- [yells] - [yells]
- [大叫] - [大叫]
- [screams]
- [尖叫声]
- Oh.
- 哦。
- What is it?
- 那是什么？
- Take a look.
- 看一看。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Oh. - Oh.
- 哦。 - 哦。
[eerie whooshing]
[阴森的呼啸声]
all: [screaming]
所有人: [尖叫]
- The ghost! It's back.
- 鬼魂！它回来了。
- I'm out of here.
- 我要离开这里。
- No, wait. We can't run.
- 不，等等。我们不能跑。
We came here to prove
我们来这里是为了证明
that we're not liars and to keep our new older friends.
我们不是骗子，并且为了保持我们新认识的大朋友们的友谊。
So let's find that stinkin' ghost!
那我们就去找那个臭鬼吧！
[eerie whooshing]
[阴森的呼啸声]
- Shh! The sounds are getting louder,
- 嘘！声音越来越大了，
and the smells are getting stronger.
而且气味也越来越浓了。
- Yeah, and it's strongest right here near this painting
- 是的，而且就在这幅画附近最强
of Great Great Great Grandpa Sal
画的是曾曾曾祖父萨尔
and Great Great Great Grandma Sylvia.
和曾曾曾祖母西尔维娅。
- Oh, what is it?
- 哦，这是什么？
- [sniffs] Smells like..
- [嗅] 闻起来像……
fish, onions, and rye bread.
鱼，洋葱，还有黑麦面包。
- Guys, look. Fish, onions, and rye bread.
伙计们，看。鱼，洋葱，还有黑麦面包。
- You know what that means?
你们知道这意味着什么吗？
The store is haunted by the spirit
这家店被曾曾曾祖母西尔维亚的灵魂缠上了。
of Great Great Great Grandma Sylvia.
等等。为什么你认为是曾曾曾祖母西尔维亚？
- Wait. Why do you think
也可能是曾曾曾祖父萨尔。
it's Great Great Great Grandma Sylvia?
是啊，但鱼、洋葱和黑麦面包
It could be Great Great Great Grandpa Sal.
不是曾曾曾祖父萨尔的。
- Yeah, but the fish, onions, and rye bread
它们是曾曾曾祖母——
aren't by Great Great Great Grandpa Sal.
好吧，我们没时间
They're by Great Great Great Grandma--
数所有的“曾”了。
- Okay, we don't have time
好的，我们没时间
for all the "greats."
去数那些'曾曾曾'了。
From now on,
从现在起，
it's just Sal and Sylvia.
就叫他们Sal和Sylvia。
all: Great.
大家都明白了。
[eerie whooshing]
（阴森的呼啸声）
- My electromagnetic field detector's going crazy.
我的电磁场探测器疯了似的响。
There's something here.
这里有什么东西。
- Ghosts give off heat.
鬼魂会散发热量。
If Sylvia's here,
如果Sylvia在这里，
I'll be able to detect her
我会用爸爸的热成像相机检测到她
using Dad's thermal camera.
用爸爸的热成像相机
[gasps]
吸气声
Dicky, don't move!
迪基，别动！
There's a ghost right behind you.
你身后有鬼
That's no ghost...
那不是鬼...
but it will haunt ya.
但会缠着你
[groaning] - Aw, jeez.
哎呀，天哪
- Can we please focus?
我们能集中注意力吗？
- We've got ghost.
我们有鬼
all: Whoa.
哇。
[cell phone dings]
[手机叮了一声]
- I'm texting Jade that they need
- 我在给Jade发短信，让他们立刻下来。
to get down here right away.
这将证明我们不是那些'哭鬼的四胞胎'。
This will prove that we aren't
[低沉的隆隆声] 大家：鬼！
just the "Quads Who Cried Ghost."
- 嗯。
[muffled rumbling] all: Ghost!
大家：爸爸？
- Mmm.
- 爸爸是鬼。
all: Dad?
爸爸是鬼？
- Dad's the ghost.
- 不。不是鬼。是那个鬼。
- Dad's a ghost?
- 爸爸是鬼？
- No. Not a ghost. The ghost.
- 不，不是鬼。是那个鬼。
- So, that means there's no ghost.
- 所以，这意味着没有鬼。
- But Dawn just said Dad's the ghost.
- 但Dawn刚刚说爸爸是鬼。
- He is. But he's not a ghost.
- 他是。但他不是鬼。
- If I may,
- 如果我可以插句话，
we mistook Dad for the ghost.
我们误把爸爸当成了鬼。
- Oh. Thank you.
- 哦。谢谢你。
Nicky.
Nicky。
[cell phone rings]
[手机铃声]
- Hey, hon, I have the toilet paper.
亲爱的，我拿到卫生纸了。
Well, I didn't realize you were still sitting there.
哦，我没意识到你还在那儿坐着。
Okay, I'm on my way.
好的，我这就过来。
- Dad hasn't been out running errands.
爸爸并没有出去跑腿。
He's been sneaking in here to play with his trains.
他一直在偷偷溜进来玩他的火车。
- Looks like we're not the only sneaker-outers in the family.
看来我们不是家里唯一偷偷摸摸的人。
[gasping]
（惊讶声）
- I can't believe Dad has a secret train room.
我简直不敢相信爸爸有一个秘密火车房。
- It's not just Dad's secret train room.
这不仅仅是爸爸的秘密火车房。
It must have been Sylvia's secret train room first.
这一定是西尔维娅的秘密火车房在先。
- But how does he have time to play with his trains
但是，他是怎么有时间玩他的火车
and go to the grocery store.
还去杂货店的？
- It's because he doesn't.
那是因为他没有。
His grocery store is right here.
他的杂货店就在这里。
- "Tom's Get Grocery"?
‘汤姆的杂货店’？
Why does he have to put "Tom's" on everything?
为什么他非得在每样东西上都加上‘汤姆的’？
- Oh [coughs]
哦，
I think I found his stink stash.
我想我找到了他的藏货。
- Well, I mean, this explains the sounds and the smell
嗯，我是说，这解释了声音和气味
but what about the lights?
但灯光是怎么回事？
- It looks like Dad's trains are incompatible
with Sylvia's old tracks.
The fuses must not be strong enough to handle it.
- So the smells, the mysterious noise,
and the flickering lights were all just Dad?
- This is good. There's no ghost.
[cell phone dings]
- Oh, no. The older kids just texted they're on their way.
- This is bad.
There's no ghost.
- That's why when they get here, ghost or no ghost,
- 这就是为什么当他们到达时，不管有没有鬼，
there's going to be a ghost here.
这里都会有一个鬼。
- If you may...
- 如果你允许的话...
- We're going to pretend that there is a ghost so the older kids don't think we're lying.
- 我们要假装这里有一个鬼，这样大孩子们就不会认为我们在撒谎。
- Thank you.
- 谢谢你。
Nicky.
尼基。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Okay, so this is where
- 好的，这就是
the ghost's presence is strongest.
鬼魂存在感最强的地方。
- So you're saying the store is haunted by the spirit
所以你是说这家店被你高高高祖母西尔维亚的鬼魂纠缠？
of your great great great grandmother Sylvia?
是的，但我们现在就叫她西尔维亚。
- Yes, but we just call her Sylvia now.
[嗖嗖声]
[whooshing]
可能这让她更生气了。
Which may have made her angrier.
哦，我们现在害怕了。
- Oh, now we're scared.
- 你们怕了吗？
- You are?
- 没有。
- Nope.
- 好吧，当你在热成像相机上看到鬼魂时，你就会害怕了。
- Well, you will be when you see the ghost on this thermal camera.
- 见鬼时刻。
- Ghost time.
[嗖嗖声] - 看见没？那就是西尔维亚。
[whooshing]
呼啸声
- See? That's Sylvia.
- 看到了吗？那是西尔维娅。
- Really? Where's Sal?
- 真的？萨尔在哪里？
[laughing]
笑声
- They're asking for Sal.
- 他们在找萨尔。
- Who's the third ghost?
- 第三个鬼是谁？
[together] Uh-oh.
一起：哎呀。
[laughter]
笑声
- [gasping]
吸气声
- Look, it's Gasper the friendly ghost.
- 看，那是友好的加斯珀鬼。
- Wait, don't go.
等等，别走。
I mean, we just wanted to be friends
我是说，我们只是非常想和你们成为朋友，
with you guys so bad, and we didn't want you to think--
我们不想让你们认为——
- You can stop right there.
你可以停在那里了。
- You were never really going to be friends.
你们从来没真的想和我们做朋友。
- What? I thought you liked us.
什么？我以为你们喜欢我们。
- We were just pretending so we could hang out here at night.
我们只是假装这样，以便晚上能在这里闲逛。
- But you guys are just...kids.
但你们只是...孩子。
[together] Kids?
孩子？
- And all this kid stuff just isn't worth it.
而这些孩子的事情根本不值得。
- Well, you can forget about giving us free movie passes now.
好吧，你现在可以忘记给我们免费电影票了。
We don't want them.
我们不想要。
You were never gonna give us free movie passes, and I know that now.
你从来就没打算给我们免费电影票，我现在知道了。
- Let's go.
我们走吧。
- I have a plan.
我有个计划。
Hold on.
等等。
- I hope it's better than your last plan.
我希望这个计划比上一个好。
- Just go with it.
就跟着做吧。
Just 'cause we're not gonna be friends
即使我们不会成为朋友
doesn't mean you guys have to go.
也不意味着你们得离开。
I mean you can still stay, hang, have fun,
我的意思是你们还是可以留下来，一起玩，开心一下，
play some laze-tag, eat some free food.
玩一些懒人标签游戏，吃点免费的食物。
- We can? [together] They can?
- 我们可以吗？[一起] 他们可以吗？
- Yes.
- 是的。
I mean, it's the least we could do
我的意思是，这是我们能做的最起码的事情
for all the trouble we've caused you.
为了我们给你们带来的所有麻烦。
We'll just hang out in our dad's office
我们会在我爸爸的办公室里闲逛
and stay out of your way.
并且尽量不打扰你们。
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
You little dudes aren't so bad.
你们这些小家伙其实还不错。
- Oh, oh, does this mean
we can be-- - No.
- You didn't let me finish.
Be friends? - No.
- At least he heard me out.
- I really hope that wasn't your plan.
- Nope. My plan involves
playing them like they played us.
And I think I know just the ghost who we can convince
to scare those punks.
So I need a volunteer. Nicky.
所以，我需要一个志愿者。尼基。
- Why me?
- 为什么是我？
- You think I'm gonna trust Stinky and Gasper over there?
- 你以为我会信任那边的斯丁基和加斯珀吗？
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Forgot something at the grocery store, Anne.
- 在杂货店忘了点东西，安妮。
I really don't want to go back,
我真的不想回去，
but I guess I have to.
但我想我不得不去。
[gasps]
[吸气声]
- So, what store are you going to?
- 那么，你要去哪家店？
Tom's Get...
汤姆的得...
Grocery?
杂货店？
Ya busted.
你露馅了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Yes!
- 是的！
- I thought you said you haven't played before.
- 我记得你说过你之前没玩过。
- No, I haven't.
- 对，我没玩过。
You guys are terrible.
你们太糟糕了。
- Woooo.
- 哇哦。
- Nice try, we know it's you, Harpers.
- 尝试不错，我们知道是你，哈珀斯。
[together] It's not us.
[一起] 不是我们。
- Wooooo.
哇哦。
- If it wasn't you, then who is it?
如果不是你们，那会是谁？
- It is I.
是我。
Sylvia.
西尔维娅。
- Sylvia?
西尔维娅？
- Sylvia!
西尔维娅！
all: [screaming]
（尖叫声）
- You have angered my spirit
你们激怒了我的灵魂，
by taking advantage of my great great great grandchildren.
利用了我的重重重重孙。
So you can play
所以你们可以玩
foosball.
玩桌上足球。
Not on my watch.
休想在我面前得逞。
[cackles]
咯咯笑
- Let's get out of here.
我们离开这里吧。
- Not before you apologize!
道歉之前别想走！
all: We're so sorry.
我们非常抱歉。
- [coughs] Tickets.
咳嗽声 票。
- And give them free movie tickets.
还要给他们免费电影票。
- Here. We're so sorry. Take the tickets.
拿着，我们真的很抱歉，拿上票。
I don't care. Whatever.
我不在乎，随便吧。
- Now...
- 现在...
Go!
走！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- That was so good. - That was so funny, Dad.
- 那真是太棒了。 - 那真是太搞笑了，爸爸。
- I guess we won't be hanging out with those guys anymore.
- 我想我们不会再和那些家伙混在一起了。
- I think we'll be just fine without them.
- 没有他们，我想我们会很好的。
- Thanks for helping us out, Dad.
- 谢谢你帮我们，爸爸。
- Well, thanks for not ratting me out to your mom.
- 嗯，谢谢你没有向你妈妈告发我。
Now can we all agree not to sneak out anymore. Deal?
现在我们能不能都同意不再偷偷溜出去了。成交？
[together] Deal. - Let's go. Come on.
[一起] 成交。 - 我们走吧。快点。
- That dress is so funny.
- 那条裙子真搞笑。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Did you do that?
- 是你做的吗？
- I didn't do that.
- 我没做。
- I did!
- 是我做的！
- The real Sylvia?
- 是真正的Sylvia吗？
- No!
- 不是！
It's your mother.
是你妈妈。
all: [screaming]
所有人: [尖叫]
- That's way scarier! - Let's go!
- 那更可怕！ - 我们走吧！
- Wait! Leave the movie tickets.
- 等等！把电影票留下。
You're grounded.
你被禁足了。
Now go!
现在走！
all: [screaming]
所有人：[尖叫]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- Hey, thanks for your help with the lights.
- 嘿，谢谢你帮忙修灯。
- And thanks for the mov-tix.
- 还有谢谢你的电影票。
- The what?
- 什么？
- Oh, dear.
- 哦，天哪。
He means movie tickets.
他是说电影票。
[laughing]
[笑]
all: [screaming]
[众人尖叫]
It goes right through me.
它直接穿过我。
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪